Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/taylor-figliuolo-765725164 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Public Speaking Communication Leadership

Languages

Italian (Limited Working)
English (Native or Bilingual)

Honors-Awards

Dean's List Cum Laude

Taylor Figliuolo

Junior Paralegal and Office Manager at McGrail & Bensinger LLP New York City Metropolitan Area

Summary

Attentive and achievement-oriented professional, experienced in both sales process and customer service duties. Ability to get along well with others, while learning new concepts quickly and effectively, coordinate in fast-paced environments, as well as portraying leadership qualities throughout my professional settings. My ultimate career goal is to grow with a company that is passionate about what they do, works above and beyond for their clients, and is known for their explicit services.

Experience

McGrail & Bensinger LLP
Junior Paralegal and Office Manager
May 2022 - Present (6 months)

LASHED

Lash Technician October 2020 - Present (2 years 1 month)

Farmingdale, New Jersey, United States

- -Provide and handcraft customized eyelash extensions to clients, in a safe and efficient manner
- -Obtain and maintain required certifications
- -Educate and explain clients about cosmetic product ingredients and their benefits
- -Recommend and sell lash aftercare products to clients to maintain service
- -Handle and resolve all customers' queries, promptly and effectively
- -Setup, clean, and organize the assigned work area for each appointment
- -Operate, clean, and disinfect all assigned equipments, properly and safely
- -Calculate and handle all costs, including product shipments and customer payments
- -Organize and schedule appointments
- -Maintain and interact with business Instagram account daily by promoting craft

Down To Earth

Manager

May 2020 - August 2021 (1 year 4 months)

Allenhurst, New Jersey, United States

- *Restaurant currently closed for the season due to Covid*
- -Hire staff and create and organize weekly schedule
- -Supervise restaurant and greet and assist customers with concerns
- -In charge of running numbers, including calculating product expenses, shipment costs, wages, and counting and closing cash registers daily

Down To Earth

Food Server

June 2019 - September 2019 (4 months)

Allenhurst, New Jersey, United States

- -Greeted and assisted customers in a fine dine experience
- -Excelled in a fast pace environment, on my feet for 10+ hours
- -Handled cash register duties

francesca's®

Lead Floor Stylist

January 2017 - March 2019 (2 years 3 months)

- -Partner with Boutique Leadership Team to support company initiatives and objects
- -Retail sales clerk known for exemplary customer service, team player mindset and exceptional cash-handling accuracy.
- -Communicate with customers about products and events to build strong connections and set standard for superior customer service
- -Took on conference calls with District Manager regarding; sales plan, operations and, visual guidance
- -Demonstrates an interest level in understanding retail sales and the relationship to inventory levels
- -Worked with wide range of retail clients to assess areas for improvement in customer service.

Simplifeye

Customer Success Intern

June 2018 - August 2018 (3 months)

New York, New York, United States

-Assist with client facing conversations via phone, email and web chat

- -Creating analytic presentations for customers
- -Help with any support overflow
- -Interacting with Salesforce, Intercom, G Suite, Excel, etc.
- -Backed by excellent interpersonal skills and a commitment to customer service that has been described as "second-to-none" by employers.

Party Perfect Event & Party Rentals

Event Coordinator

June 2015 - March 2018 (2 years 10 months)

- -Supervise groups of 20-250 children while ensuring a safe and positive environment
- -Leading staff of up to 20 people and maximizing efficiency
- -Worked well with entire facility team to ensure parties meet and exceed guest expectations
- -Educate employees on how to work and operate all rentals

Easy Pickens

Sales Associate

November 2014 - April 2015 (6 months)

- -Provide customer service by greeting and assisting customers, and responding to customer inquiries and complaints.
- -Handled cash register responsibilities, as well as maintaining a neat and clean store for customers daily
- -Monitor sales activities to ensure that customers receive satisfactory service and quality purchases.

Manalapan Recreation Center

Camp Counselor

June 2013 - August 2014 (1 year 3 months)

- -Provided leadership to campers in grades kindergarten through seventh
- -Supervised over 50 campers daily ages 10-14
- -Organized daily games and activities while ensuring safety of the children

Education

Rutgers University–New Brunswick

Bachelor of Arts - BA, Criminal Justice and Sociology · (2017 - 2020)

Brookdale Community College

Business and Personal/Financial Services Marketing Operations · (2016 - 2017)

University of Tampa
Liberal Arts and Sciences/Liberal Studies · (2015 - 2015)

Saint John Vianney High School (2010 - 2015)